Guide to the Frank Espada photographs and papers, 1946-2010 and undated, bulk 1964-2000 RL.00367
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Puerto Rican Diaspora, 1965-1989 and undated; 30 Linear Feet 41 boxes Approximately 12,323 items
  - Connecticut, 1981-1982; 518 items
    - Finished Prints, 1981-1982; 30 prints
      - Roberto Laboy, former gang member, Hartford (Print 131), 1981 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0173)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/4 x 11 1/4 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
      - Comerio Restaurant, Park Street, Hartford (Print 102), 1981 (Box 18, Image RL.00367-P-0174)
        Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 20 inches
      - Couple on their stoop, Hartford (Print 142), 1982 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0175)
        Image dimensions: 8 7/8 x 13 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
      - Angel, president of Young Nomads, Hartford (Print 127), 1982 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0176)
      - Angel and Lenny on Word Street, Hartford (Print 167), 1982 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0177)
        Image dimensions: 8 3/4 x 13 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
      - Christ for Sale, Hartford (Print 146), 1982 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0178)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
      - Christ for Sale, Hartford (Print 146), 1982 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0179)
      - Hartford, 1981 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0180)
        Image dimensions: 8 7/8 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
      - Hartford (Print 7039), 1981 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0181)
      - Hartford, 1981 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0182)
        Image dimensions: 8 5/8 x 13 1/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
    - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1981-1982; 488 items
      - Work prints: Hartford 1 (folder 1 of 2), 1982; 131 items (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Hartford 1 (folder 2 of 2), 1982; 157 items (Box 21, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: Hartford 2 (folder 1 of 3), circa 1982; 50 items (Box 21, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Hartford 2 (folder 2 of 3), circa 1982; 50 items (Box 21, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Hartford 2 (folder 3 of 3), circa 1982; 31 items (Box 21, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: Hartford Centro, circa 1982; 34 items (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Eugenio Caro, Hartford, 1981; 25 items (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Savage Nomads, Hartford, 1981; 10 items (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Hawaii, 1980-1981; 1840 items
    - Finished Prints, 1980-1981; 9 prints
      - Nancy Ortiz, Oahu, 1980 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0183)
        Image dimensions: 6 3/4 x 9 5/8 inches; sheet dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
      - Santa Rodriguez, Hawaii, 1980 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0184)
        Image dimensions: 9 5/8 x 6/5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 10 x 8 inches
      - Joe and Mina Velez, Big Island, 1981 (Box 24, Image RL.00367-P-0185)
        Image dimensions: 7 3/8 x 11 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 16 inches
      - Blase Souza, second generation, historian of Puerto Rican experience in Hawaii, founder of Puerto Rican Heritage Society, Honolulu (Print 62), 1981 (Box 24, Image RL.00367-P-0186)
        Image dimensions: 11 3/8 x 7 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - Hawaii, 1980 (Box 24, Image RL.00367-P-0187)
        Image dimensions: 11 x 7 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - Santa Rochyuez, first generation Hawaiian-Puerto Rican, in front of her lava oven, Kukuihaele Plantation (Print 173), 1981 (Box 24, Image RL.00367-P-0188)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/8 x 7 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - Walter-Shinka house, a drug rehabilitation half-way house in Honolulu (Print 91), 1981 (Box 24, Image RL.00367-P-0189)
        Image dimensions: 11 3/8 x 7 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - Confessor Riviera, second generation Hawaiian-Puerto Rican, with experimental cutting on his farm, Kona Coast of the Big Island (Print 3), circa 1980 (Box 24, Image RL.00367-P-0190)
      - Fans at Puerto Rican Softball League tournament, Honolulu (Print 169), 1981 (Box 22, Image RL.00367-P-0191)
    - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1980-1981; 1831 items
      - Hawaii, contact sheets HI 1-39, missing HI 28, 32, 35, 1981; 36 items (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Hawaii, contact sheets HI 40-71, missing HI 44, 48, 52, 68, 1981; 28 items (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Hawaii, various subjects, 1981 April; 108 items (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: Kohala Farmers, 1981 April; 78 items (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Kona Farmers, 1981 April; 57 items (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Work prints: Santos Caravalho, 1981 April; 34 items (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Johnny Matias, 1981 April; 32 items (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: Shinko House, 1981 April; 64 items (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Hawaii, Puerto Rican Softball League, 1981 April; 87 items (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Young People in Hawaii; Nancy Perry (radio station), 1981 April; 52 items (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (folder 1 of 5), 1980; 50 items (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (folder 2 of 5), 1980; 36 items (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (folder 3 of 5), 1980; 38 items (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (folder 4 of 5), 1980; 33 items (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (folder 5 of 5), 1980; 12 items (Box 25, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 1 of 10), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 2 of 10), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 8)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 3 of 10), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 4 of 10), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 5 of 10), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 6 of 10), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 7 of 10), 1980-1981; 41 items (Box 25, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 8 of 10), 1980-1981; 41 items (Box 25, Folder 14)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 9 of 10), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 15)
      - Work prints: The Hawaiian Experience (folder 10 of 10), 1980-1981; 19 items (Box 25, Folder 16)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 1 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 17)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 2 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 25, Folder 18)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 3 of 18), 1980-1981; 39 items (Box 25, Folder 19)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 4 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 5 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 6 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 7 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 8 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 9 of 18), 1980-1981; 42 items (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 10 of 18), 1980-1981; 43 items (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 11 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 12 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 13 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 14 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 15 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 16 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 17 of 18), 1980-1981; 40 items (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Work prints: Hawaii (2) (folder 18 of 18), 1980-1981; 21 items (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Massachusetts, 1979; 1 items
    - Finished Prints
      - Carlos Esteban, Puerto Rican ex-political prisoner in Chile, English teacher in community social program, Roxbury (Print 49), 1979 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0192)
        Image dimensions: 7 5/8 x 11 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 16 inches
  - New Jersey, 1981-1982; 314 items
    - Finished Prints, 1981-1982; 3 prints
      - Jersey City, 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0193)
      - Newark, circa 1981 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0194)
      - Eladio Rodriguez, proprietor of El Gallito Restaurant, Jersey City (Print 113), 1982 (Box 20, Image RL.00367-P-0195)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 inches; mount dimensions: 13x 15 7/8 inches
    - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1980-1981; 311 items
      - Comite de Apoyo a los Trabajadores Agricolas (CATA), Glassboro-Vineland, contact sheets GL 1-15, 1981; 15 items (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Work prints: CATA, Glassboro-Vineland (folder 1 of 3), 1981; 50 items (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Work prints: CATA, Glassboro-Vineland (folder 2 of 3), 1981; 50 items (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Work prints: CATA, Glassboro-Vineland (folder 3 of 3), 1981; 11 items (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Comite de Apoyo a los Trabajadores Agricolas (CATA), ACLU Farmworkers Project, Glassboro (folder 1 of 2), 1981; 50 items (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: CATA, ACLU Farmworkers Project, Glassboro (folder 2 of 2), 1981; 48 items (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Eladio, El Gallito Restaurant, Jersey City, 1980; 17 items (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Jersey City, Newark (folder 1 of 2), 1980; 50 items (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Jersey City, Newark (folder 2 of 2), 1980; 20 items (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - New York, 1965-1989; 3771 items
    - Finished Prints, 1965-1985; 69 prints
      - Tomás Hernandez, New York City, 1978 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0196)
        Image dimensions: 6 3/8 x 9 1/2 inches; sheet dimensions: 7 x 10 inches
      - Miriam Colón, New York City, 1982 (Box 6, Image RL.00367-P-0197)
        Image dimensions: 6 x 8 3/4 inches; sheet dimensions: 8 x 10 inches
      - Nancy at PROMESA group session, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0198)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/2 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Cindy at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0199)
        Image dimensions: 8 1/2 x 12 3/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Louise at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0200)
        Image dimensions: 8 1/8 x 12 1/4 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Richard at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0201)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 3/4 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Jane at group session, PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0202)
        Image dimensions: 13 3/4 x 9 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Group session, PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0203)
        Image dimensions: 8 1/4 x 12 1/4 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Group session, PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 July (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0204)
        Image dimensions: 7 5/8 x 11 3/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Group session, PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0205)
        Image dimensions: 7 5/8 x 11 1/2 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Students at PROMESA High School, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0206)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 3/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Rick at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0207)
      - Trimming the tree, PROMESA, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0208)
        Image dimensions: 7 3/8 x 11 1/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Julio, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0209)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 5/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - At PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0210)
        Image dimensions: 8 1/2 x 5 5/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Group session at PROMESA, 1974 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0211)
        Image dimensions: 9 1/4 x 13 1/2 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Group session, PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0212)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 1/2 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Jane and Julio, PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0213)
        Image dimensions: 8 3/8 x 12 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Duke, at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0214)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 1/4 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Enrique, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0215)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/4 x 8 inches; sheet size: 14 x 11 inches
      - Peter at PROMESA, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0216)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/4 x 7 5/8 inches; sheet size: 14 x 11 inches
      - Ady at PROMESA group session, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0217)
        Image dimensions: 8 3/4 x 11 3/4 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Rafael at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0218)
      - Lucille at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0219)
      - Dana at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0220)
        Image dimensions: 11 3/8 x 7 1/2 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Jill at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0221)
      - Alba at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0222)
        Image dimensions: 13 5/8 x 9 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - At PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0223)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 10 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Doris at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0224)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/4 x 7 1/2 inches; sheet size: 14 x 11 inches
      - East Harlem, 1974 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0225)
      - East Harlem, 1974 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0226)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/8 x 7 5/8 inches; sheet size: 14 x 11 inches
      - East Harlem, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0227)
      - Manhattan Village, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0228)
      - East Harlem, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0229)
        Image dimensions: 8 1/4 x 5 5/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11
      - Ballet Hispanico, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0230)
        Image dimensions: 9 1/4 x 6 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 11 inches
      - South Bronx, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0231)
      - PROMESA, South Bronx, circa 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0232)
      - Manhattan Valley, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0233)
      - Ballet Hispanico, 1982 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0234)
        Image dimensions: 9 3/4 x 12 1/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - Manhattan Village, 1982 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0235)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 3/8 inches; sheet size: 11 x 14 inches
      - PROMESA, South Bronx, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0236)
      - PROMESA, South Bronx, 1981 (Box 29, Image RL.00367-P-0237)
      - Grace, resident at PROMESA, South Bronx (Print 30), 1981 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0238)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 15 7/8 inches
      - Alberto, resident at PROMESA, South Bronx (Print 31), 1981 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0239)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 15 7/8 inches
      - PROMESA, South Bronx, 1981 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0240)
        Image dimensions: 7 1/2 x 11 inches; mount dimensions: 12 7/8 x 15 7/8 inches
      - Grace, resident of PROMESA, South Bronx (duplicate of Print 30), 1981 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0241)
      - Miriam Colon, founder and director of Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre (Print 40), 1981 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0242)
      - Going to Puerto Rico for the first time, New York City (duplicate of Print 107), 1981 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0243)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/2 x 7 5/8; mount dimensions: 16 x 13 inches
      - Young boy with baby carriage, East New York, Brooklyn, 1965 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0244)
        Image dimensions: 7 5/8 x 11 1/8 inches; mount dimensions: 13 x 16 inches
      - Jane at group session, PROMESA, South Bronx, 1985 (Box 27, Image RL.00367-P-0245)
      - Going to Puerto Rico for the first time, New York City (Print 107), 1972 (Box 30, Image RL.00367-P-0246)
        Image dimensions: 13 5/8 x 9 inches; mount dimensions: 19 7/8 x 16 inches
      - Sandwich assembly line, food processing plant, South Bronx (Print 105), 1981 (Box 30, Image RL.00367-P-0247)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 5/8; mount dimensions: 14 x 20 inches
      - Students at Boricua College, a bilingual bi-cultural institution, Brooklyn (Print 221), 1983 (Box 30, Image RL.00367-P-0248)
        Image dimensions: 13 1/2 x 9 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 16 inches
      - Reading time in a bilingual classroom, East Harlem (Print 121), 1982 (Box 30, Image RL.00367-P-0249)
      - Patrolman Carlos Gonzales, New York Police Dept., in locker room of 79th precinct station house, Brooklyn (Print 119), 1982 (Box 31, Image RL.00367-P-0250)
        Image dimension: 8 7/8 x 13 3/8 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
      - South Bronx, 1981 (Box 31, Image RL.00367-P-0251)
        Image dimensions: 9 3/4 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
      - Homeless program resident at PROMESA, Bronx (Print 244), 1983 (Box 31, Image RL.00367-P-0252)
        Image dimensions: 9 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions 14 x 19 inches
      - PROMESA, South Bronx, 1974 (Box 31, Image RL.00367-P-0253)
      - PROMESA, South Bronx, circa 1980 (Box 31, Image RL.00367-P-0254)
      - Doris at PROMESA, South Bronx, circa 1981 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0255)
        Image dimensions: 17 x 14 inches; mount dimensions: 11 x 7 1/2 inches
      - Bilingual class, East Harlem (Print 120), circa 1981 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0256)
      - Waiting for mediator at PROMESA, South Bronx, 1981 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0257)
      - Ballet Hispanico (Print 191), 1981 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0258)
      - Miriam Colon, 1982 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0259)
      - Maria, Brooklyn, 1965 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0260)
      - Sister Theresa - Pentecostal Service, Brooklyn, 1965 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0261)
        Image dimensions: 8 3/4 x 13 1/2 inches; mount dimensions: 14 x 19 inches
      - Jose Acuna, community organizer, in building burned by arson, Manhattan, 1981 (Box 32, Image RL.00367-P-0262)
      - No known title [from Three King's Day, East Harlem], 1981 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0321)
        Image dimensions: 11 1/8 x 16 7/8 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 24 inches
      - Brooklyn, 1984 (Box 54, Image RL.00367-P-0322)
        Image dimensions: 12 1/4 x 18 inches; mount dimensions: 20 x 24 inches
    - Contact Sheets and Work Prints, 1974-1989; 3702 items
      - Ballet Hispanico, contact sheets NY 1-28, 1981 January; 28 items (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Ballet Hispanico, contact sheets NY 134-140, missing 135, 1981 January; 6 items (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (folder 1 of 4), 1981 January; 150 items (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (folder 2 of 4), 1981 January; 118 items (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (folder 3 of 4), 1981 January; 96 items (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (folder 4 of 4), 1981 January; 79 items (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (1) (folder 1 of 4), 1981 January; 40 items (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (1) (folder 2 of 4), 1981 January; 40 items (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (1) (folder 3 of 4), 1981 January; 40 items (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (1) (folder 4 of 4), 1981 January; 26 items (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (2) (folder 1 of 4), 1981 January; 40 items (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (2) (folder 2 of 4), 1981 January; 40 items (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (2) (folder 3 of 4), 1981 January; 40 items (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (2) (folder 4 of 4), 1981 January; 42 items (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (3), 1981 January; 21 items (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (4) (folder 1 of 2), 1981 January; 50 items (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Ballet Hispanico (4) (folder 2 of 2), 1981 January; 51 items (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre, contact sheets NY 29-37, 1981 January; 9 items (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre, 1981 January; 61 items (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre (1) (folder 1 of 2), 1981 January; 40 items (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Puerto Rican Traveling Theatre (1) (folder 2 of 2), 1981 January; 17 items (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - East Harlem Music School, contact sheets NY 55-67, missing 62, 1980 December; 12 items (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: East Harlem Music School (folder 1 of 3), 1980 December; 61 items (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Work prints: East Harlem Music School (folder 2 of 3), 1980 December; 60 items (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Work prints: East Harlem Music School (folder 3 of 3), 1980 December; 81 items (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Work prints: East Harlem Music School (1), 1980 December; 29 items (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Promesa, South Bronx, contact sheets NY 68-100, 1980-1981; 33 items (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 1 of 3), 1980-1981; 57 items (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 2 of 3), 1980-1981; 59 items (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 3 of 3), 1980-1981; 48 items (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 1 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 2 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 3 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 4 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 5 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 6 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 7 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 8 of 17), 1974; 41 items (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 9 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 10 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 11 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 12 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 13 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 14 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 15 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 16 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Work prints: Promesa, South Bronx (folder 17 of 17), 1974; 40 items (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Manhattan Valley, contact sheets NY 102-110, 141-156, 1981; 25 items (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Work prints: Manhattan Valley (folder 1 of 3), 1981; 64 items (Box 35, Folder 8)